Guide to the William Hewlett Papers M1995
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4: Properties and Rentals, 1946-2006
  - San Felipe Ranches: Property Taxes (part 2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 635, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Property Taxes (part 1 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 636, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Property Taxes (part 2 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 636, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Property Taxes, 1997 (Box 636, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Ranch Appraisals, 1977 (Box 636, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Ranch Appraisals, 1983-1986 (Box 636, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Sale, Distribution, Dissolution Agreement, 1997 (Box 636, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Bank Reconciliations, 1992-1993 (Box 636, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Bank Reconciliations, 1993 (Box 636, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Bank Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 636, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Bank Statements, 1992 (Box 636, Folder 10)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Bank Statements, 1994-1995 (Box 636, Folder 11)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Bank Statements, 1997 (Box 636, Folder 12)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Bank Statements, 1998-1999 (Box 636, Folder 13)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 1989 (Box 636, Folder 14)
    These were meetings of the Hewlett and Packard families. Originally shareholders were David Packard, William Hewlett, and Flora Hewlett. Gradually the children of both families also became Shareholders and took on more leadership roles. The meetings regarded the operation of the Ranches - operating budgets, Board By-Laws, future of the ranches, composition of the Board, rights of the shareholders, ways to avoid passing on financial burdens to future generations, as well what the purpose of the ranch should be: land and wildlife conservation, historic cattle ranch and personal residences.
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 1989-1991 (Box 636, Folder 15)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 636, Folder 16)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 1991 (Box 637, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 1992 (Box 637, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 1 of 2), 1993 (Box 637, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 2 of 2), 1993 (Box 637, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 637, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 1994 (Box 637, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 637, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 1995 (Box 637, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 637, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 2003 (Box 637, Folder 10)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 1 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 637, Folder 11)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 2 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 637, Folder 12)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 2004 (Box 637, Folder 13)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 2004-2005 (Box 638, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 1 of 4), 2005 (Box 638, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 2 of 4), 2005 (Box 638, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 3 of 4), 2005 (Box 638, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 4 of 4), 2005 (Box 638, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings, 2005-2006 (Box 638, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 1 of 4), 2006 (Box 638, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 2 of 4), 2006 (Box 638, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 3 of 4), 2006 (Box 638, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board and Shareholders Meetings (part 4 of 4), 2006 (Box 638, Folder 10)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 1 of 5), 2004 (Box 638, Folder 11)
    The Conference calls were between the members of the Board (the Hewlett and Packard families) and a facilitator, who helped finalize a plan for the future of the ranch. This plan attempted to protect the future generations from assuming financial burdens from the ranch, provided the option for a limited number of personal residences on the ranch, for continued cattle ranching operations and a conservation easement protecting the land with The Nature Conservancy.
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 2 of 5), 2004 (Box 639, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 3 of 5), 2004 (Box 639, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 4 of 5), 2004 (Box 639, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 5 of 5), 2004 (Box 639, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 1 of 5), 2005 (Box 639, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 2 of 5), 2005 (Box 639, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 3 of 5), 2005 (Box 639, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 4 of 5), 2005 (Box 639, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 5 of 5), 2005 (Box 639, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 1 of 2), 2006 (Box 639, Folder 10)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Board Conference Calls (part 2 of 2), 2006 (Box 640, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 640, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Budget, 1990 (Box 640, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Budget, 1990-1992 (Box 640, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 640, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 640, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 640, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Building Estimates, 1969 (Box 640, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Capital Items, 1989 (Box 640, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Cash Receipts, 1988 (Box 640, Folder 10)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Cash Receipts, 1988-1989 (Box 640, Folder 11)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Cash Receipts, 1989-1990 (Box 640, Folder 12)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Cash Receipts, 1991 (Box 640, Folder 13)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Cash Receipts, 1991-1992 (Box 640, Folder 14)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Cash Receipts, 1994 (Box 640, Folder 15)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Cash Receipts, 1995 (Box 640, Folder 16)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Cash Receipts, 1997 (Box 640, Folder 17)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Cash Receipts, 1998 (Box 641, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Coe Ranch Ranch Appraisal, 1996 (Box 641, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Coe Ranch Ranch Property Taxes, 1996-1997 (Box 641, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Coe Ranch Ranch Property Taxes, 1997 (Box 641, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Corporate 1099 Forms, 1990-1991 (Box 641, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Corporate 1099 Forms, 1991-1998 (Box 641, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 641, Folder 7)
    Contains correspondence, photographs of the ranch, and some reference material. Some correspondence is David Packard's.
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 641, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Correspondence, 1992 (Box 641, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Correspondence, 1993 (Box 642, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 642, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 642, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Cost Accounting, 1993-1996 (Box 642, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Equipment, 1988 (Box 642, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Facilitator Search, 2004 (Box 642, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Forgiven Loan, 1990-1992 (Box 642, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger, 1989 (Box 642, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger, 1990 (Box 642, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger, 1991 (Box 642, Folder 10)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger, 1992 (Box 643, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 1 of 4), 1993 (Box 643, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 2 of 4), 1993 (Box 643, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 3 of 4), 1993 (Box 643, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 4 of 4), 1993 (Box 643, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 643, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 644, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 1 of 2), 1995 (Box 644, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 2 of 2), 1995 (Box 644, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 1 of 3), 1997 (Box 644, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 2 of 3), 1997 (Box 644, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 3 of 3), 1997 (Box 644, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 1 of 3), 1998-1999 (Box 645, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 2 of 3), 1998-1999 (Box 645, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General Ledger (part 3 of 3), 1998-1999 (Box 645, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: General, 1967, 1988-1989 (Box 645, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Gift to Henry Coe State Park, 1991-1993 (Box 645, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: House Heating Plan, undated (Box 645, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Hunt Club, 1992-1993 (Box 645, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Hunt Club, 1995-1998 (Box 645, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Library Benefit Assesment Appeal, 1996-1997 (Box 645, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Maps, 1978-1993 (Box 646, Folder 1)
    Oversize material was separated and moved to Map Folder 13.
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Newfron, 1996-1999 (Box 646, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Old Maps, undated (Box 646, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Packwood Valley Potential Dam Site, 1993 (Box 646, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Property Taxes, 1989-1990 (Box 646, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Property Taxes, 1991-1992 (Box 646, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Property Taxes, 1992-1993 (Box 646, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Property Taxes, 1994-1995 (Box 646, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Property Taxes, 1995-1996 (Box 646, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Property Taxes, 1997-1998 (Box 646, Folder 10)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Property Taxes, 1997-1999 (Box 646, Folder 11)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Property Taxes, 1998-1999 (Box 647, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Return/Report of Employee Benefit Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 647, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Review of Budget Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 647, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Santa Clara Valley Water District Precipitation Station, 1977-1979 (Box 647, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Swimming Pool, 1969-1985 (Box 647, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Swimming Pool Solar Heating, 1977 (Box 647, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1987-1988 (Box 647, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1988-1989 (Box 647, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1989-1990 (Box 647, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1990-1991 (Box 647, Folder 10)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1991-1992 (Box 647, Folder 11)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1992-1993 (Box 648, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1993-1994 (Box 648, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1994-1995 (Box 648, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1995-1996 (Box 648, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1996-1997 (Box 648, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return (part 1 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 648, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return (part 2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 648, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1998-1999 (Box 649, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Tax Return, 1999-2000 (Box 649, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Santa Clara Ranch: Wild Turkeys, 1982-1986 (Box 649, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Section 743(b) Step-up Summary (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 649, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Section 743(b) Step-up Summary (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 649, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Service Contract, 1998 (Box 649, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: State of California Licenses for Dams, 1985-1988 (Box 649, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Statement by Domestic Stock Corporation, 1987 (Box 649, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Stock Certificates, 1983 (Box 649, Folder 10)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Subscriptions, 1987 (Box 649, Folder 11)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Sunnyside-San Felipe Trust: Estimated Taxes, 1992 (Box 649, Folder 12)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Sunnyside-San Felipe Trust: General, 1989-1995 (Box 649, Folder 13)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Sunnyside-San Felipe Trust: Lake Tahoe Property Easements, 1976-1990 (Box 649, Folder 14)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Sunnyside-San Felipe Trust: Tax Return File, 1991-1992 (Box 650, Folder 1)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Suspense Accounts Current, 1989 (Box 650, Folder 2)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Tax Returns (part 1 of 3), 1979-1994 (Box 650, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Tax Returns (part 2 of 3), 1979-1994 (Box 650, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Tax Returns (part 3 of 3), 1979-1994 (Box 650, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: U.S. Bank Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 650, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Vendor List, 1989 (Box 650, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Washoe County Property Appraisal, 1993 (Box 650, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Water (part 1 of 3), 1959-1982 (Box 650, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Water (part 2 of 3), 1959-1982 (Box 651, Folder 1)
    Includes correspondence, photographic negatives of ranch land, applications, permits, and other official documents.
  - San Felipe Ranches: Water (part 3 of 3), 1959-1982 (Box 651, Folder 2)
    Oversize material was separated and moved to Map Folders 3 and 11.
  - San Felipe Ranches: Water, 1978-1985 (Box 651, Folder 3)
  - San Felipe Ranches: Wells Fargo, 1986-1996 (Box 651, Folder 4)
  - San Felipe Ranches: West One Conversion to U.S. Bank, 1996-1998 (Box 651, Folder 5)
  - San Felipe Ranches: William Hewlett and Dave Packard Cattle, 1989-1991 (Box 651, Folder 6)
  - San Felipe Ranches: William Hewlett and Dave Packard Cattle, 1990-1991 (Box 651, Folder 7)
  - San Felipe Ranches: William Hewlett and Dave Packard Cattle, 1992 (Box 651, Folder 8)
  - San Felipe Ranches: William Hewlett and Dave Packard Cattle, 1993 (Box 651, Folder 9)
  - San Felipe Ranches: William Hewlett and Dave Packard Cattle, 1994 (Box 651, Folder 10)
  - San Felipe Ranches: William Hewlett Requests, 1972-1973 (Box 651, Folder 11)
  - Sequoia National Forest: Proposed Lion Meadows Acquisition, 1974-1976 (Box 651, Folder 12)
  - Sharon Oaks Condo: Bills, 1984-1989 (Box 651, Folder 13)
  - Sharon Oaks Condo: Sale of Condo, 1990 (Box 651, Folder 14)
  - Sharon Oaks Condo: Sharon Oaks Association, 1985-1990 (Box 651, Folder 15)
  - Sharon Oaks Condo: Tenant, 1984-1988 (Box 652, Folder 1)
  - Shepherds Knoll Association: Bills, 1984-1990 (Box 652, Folder 2)
  - Shepherds Knoll Association: Bills, 1992-1996 (Box 652, Folder 3)
  - Shepherds Knoll Association: Bills, 1997-1999 (Box 652, Folder 4)
  - Shepherds Knoll Association: Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 652, Folder 5)
  - Shepherds Knoll Association: Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 652, Folder 6)
  - Shepherds Knoll Association: Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 652, Folder 7)
  - Shepherds Knoll Association: Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 653, Folder 1)
  - Shepherds Knoll Association: Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 653, Folder 2)
  - Shepherds Knoll Association: Owners and Board of Directors, 1989-1994 (Box 653, Folder 3)
  - Shepherds Knoll Association: Property Taxes and Expenses, 1991-1995 (Box 653, Folder 4)
  - Sugar Bowl: 1982 Cash Flow Forecast and 1983 to 1985 Anticipated Capital Expenditures (Box 653, Folder 5)
  - Sugar Bowl: Audit Reports, 1967-1970 (Box 653, Folder 6)
  - Sugar Bowl: Audit Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 653, Folder 7)
  - Sugar Bowl: Bills, 1959-1964 (Box 653, Folder 8)
  - Sugar Bowl: Bills, 1966-1970 (Box 653, Folder 9)
  - Sugar Bowl: Bills, 1971-1974 (Box 653, Folder 10)
  - Sugar Bowl: Bills, 1976-1982 (Box 653, Folder 11)
  - Sugar Bowl: Bills, 1983-1987 (Box 654, Folder 1)
  - Sugar Bowl: Bills, 1988-1991 (Box 654, Folder 2)
    Contains bills, ledger pages, copies of checks, and some photographs of repairs on the property.
  - Sugar Bowl: Bills, 1992-1994 (Box 654, Folder 3)
  - Sugar Bowl: Bills, 1996 (Box 654, Folder 4)
  - Sugar Bowl: Bills, 1998 (Box 654, Folder 5)
  - Sugar Bowl: Bills, 1999-2001 (Box 654, Folder 6)
  - Sugar Bowl: Board Meetings Minutes, 1965-1968 (Box 654, Folder 7)
  - Sugar Bowl: Board Meetings Minutes, 1969-1973 (Box 655, Folder 1)
  - Sugar Bowl: Board Meetings Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 655, Folder 2)
  - Sugar Bowl: Board Meetings Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 655, Folder 3)
  - Sugar Bowl: Board Meetings Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 655, Folder 4)
  - Sugar Bowl: Board Meetings Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 655, Folder 5)
  - Sugar Bowl: Board Meetings Minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 655, Folder 6)
  - Sugar Bowl: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 655, Folder 7)
  - Sugar Bowl: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 655, Folder 8)
  - Sugar Bowl: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 655, Folder 9)
  - Sugar Bowl: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 656, Folder 1)
  - Sugar Bowl: Development Program Guarantor for Canadian Bank of Commerce Loan, 1962-1982 (Box 656, Folder 2)
  - Sugar Bowl: Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, 1975-1977 (Box 656, Folder 3)
  - Sugar Bowl: Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, 1977-1980 (Box 656, Folder 4)
  - Sugar Bowl: Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, 1980-1981 (Box 656, Folder 5)
  - Sugar Bowl: Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, 1981-1982 (Box 656, Folder 6)
  - Sugar Bowl: Master Plan (part 1 of 2), 1988 (Box 656, Folder 7)
  - Sugar Bowl: Master Plan (part 2 of 2), 1988 (Box 657, Folder 1)
    Oversize material was separated and moved to Map Folder 11.
  - Sugar Bowl: Personal Property Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 657, Folder 2)
    Contains correspondence regarding Hewlett's house at the Sugar Bowl. Mainly about repairs, complaints, guests, and similar issues.
  - Sugar Bowl: Personal Property Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 657, Folder 3)
  - Sugar Bowl: Personal Property Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 657, Folder 4)
  - Sugar Bowl: Ten Year Analysis and Review of Operations, 1975 (Box 657, Folder 5)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: Bills and Owners Statements, 1978-1990 (Box 657, Folder 6)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: Correspondence and Bills, 1966-1980 (Box 657, Folder 7)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: Correspondence and Bills, 1982 (Box 657, Folder 8)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: Correspondence and Minutes, 1972-1976 (Box 658, Folder 1)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: Correspondence and Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 658, Folder 2)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: Correspondence and Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 658, Folder 3)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: Correspondence, Minutes, and Proposal, 1965-1977 (Box 658, Folder 4)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: Costs and Income Statements, 1972-1980 (Box 658, Folder 5)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: Costs and Income Statements, 1991 (Box 658, Folder 6)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: General (part 1 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box 658, Folder 7)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: General (part 2 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box 658, Folder 8)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: General, 1977 (Box 658, Folder 9)
  - Sun Valley Condominiums: Lodge I and II Condos, 1978-1983 (Box 659, Folder 1)
  - Sun Valley House: Architect, 1995 (Box 659, Folder 2)
  - Sun Valley House: Bills, 1991 (Box 659, Folder 3)
  - Sunnyside Properties, 1999 (Box 659, Folder 4)
  - Vacant Lot Number 8, 1999 (Box 659, Folder 5)
- Series 5: Biographical and Family History, 1946-2003
  Contains biographies, photographs, articles, newspaper clippings, photocopied material, obituaries, correspondence, cards, and oral history interviews. These papers provide documentation of events in Hewlett's life and background, as well as on some family history. Some of the material was filed by Hewlett's assistant Mollie Yoshizumi, compiled posthumously after Hewlett passed away.
  - Biographical Data, Who's Who in California and American Men in Science, 1964-1999 (Box 659, Folder 6)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1953-1956 (Box 659, Folder 7)
  - Biographies (part 1 of 2), 1982, 1988-2001 (Box 659, Folder 8)
  - Biographies (part 2 of 2), 1982, 1988-2001 (Box 659, Folder 9)
  - Biographies and Resumes, 1996-2001 (Box 659, Folder 10)
  - Biography and Hewlett-Packard Office, 2001-2003 (Box 659, Folder 11)
  - Biography Sheets (part 1 of 2), 1963-1993 (Box 659, Folder 12)
  - Biography Sheets (part 2 of 2), 1963-1993 (Box 660, Folder 1)
  - Birthday Celebration, 1978 (Box 660, Folder 2)
    Contains correspondence, sheet music, and photographs of Hewlett's birthday celebration at Hewlett-Packard headquarters.
  - Birthday Party (80th) Invitation List, 1993 (Box 660, Folder 3)
  - Business Cards (Director Emeritus), undated (Box 660, Folder 4)